https://www.coloradopen.com/privacy

Menu
Search
Cart
E-Gift CertificateWork-a-DayBeginning WritersShop Our Brands
A - L
5280
5280 Ambassador Collection5280 Aspen Collection5280 Aspire Collection5280 Ebonite5280 Majestic Collection5280 Opera
American Pen Company
Bronze MinimalistBallpoint WritingLiquid Ink Ball WritingLimited Edition Valentine's SetFountain Pen WritingIndependence Signature TipLeather FoliosLeather CasesSketch Pencil and Highlighting
Aurora
Aurora Ipsilon DemoAurora Duo Cart Fountain PenAurora Fountain PensAurora Rollerballs
BENU
BrioletteMinimaTattoo
Conklin
Conklin All American Turquoise SerenityConklin All American Golden WalnutConklin Limited Edition Endura Abalone RosegoldConklin DuraFlex DemonstratorConklin All American Courage Ltd. Ed.Conklin Limited Edition All American EbonyConklin Heritage Word GaugeConklin Duraflex Limited Edition ElementsConklin All American
Cross
Cross 2020 Year of the RatCross Townsend for Scuderia FerrariCross ApogeeCross WanderlustCross Bailey LightCross ATXCross Century IICross TownsendCross Tech3+ Multi-PenCross X SeriesCross BallpointsCross Fountain PensCross Rollerballs
Esterbrook
Esterbrook Estie Maraschino CherryEsterbrook Phaeton SetEsterbrook JRCamden CompositionEsterbrook EstieEsterbrook SparkleEsterbrook Nook
Fisher
Fisher Red & Blue Line Cap-O-MaticFisher BrassSpecial Edition Bullet 50th Anniversary Apollo 11Fisher S.E. Cap-O-Matic 50th Anniversary Apollo 11Fisher Clutch Space PenFisher Original Astronaut Space PenFisher Bullet Space PenFisher Telescoping Space PenFisher X-750 Stylus
LeBOEUF
LeBOEUF PilgrimLeBOEUF Springfield
M - P
Montegrappa
Montegrappa Tulip for Team FoxMontegrappa Copper MuleMontegrappa BallpointsMontegrappa Fountain PensMontegrappa Rollerballs
Monteverde
Monteverde MegaMonteverde 20th Anniversary Limited Edition InnovaMonteverde Limited Edition Regatta ExplorersMonteverde Monza 3Monteverde Regatta Sport AlluraMonteverde Sweet LifeMonteverde RitmaMonteverde Tool Pen EdgeMonteverde ImpressaMonteverde Aldo DomaniMonteverde Giant SequoiaMonteverde PrimaMonteverde Ballpoint PensMonteverde Fountain PensMonteverde Rollerball Pens
Padrino
Padrino TrendPadrino GridPadrino Fiore Pen SetPadrino Multi-PenPadrino Pixie
Parker
Parker Duofold ClassicParker Sonnet SterlingParker Sonnet CoreParker Jotter XLParker JotterParker BallpointsParker Fountain PensParker Rollerballs
Pineider
Pineider Back To The Future Limited EditionPineider HoneycombPineider Avatar URPineider Avatar UR DemonstratorPineider Hollywood Journal
Q - T
Regal
Regal British MuseumRegal CrownRegal ElizabethRegal Henry
S.T. Dupont
S.T. Dupont DéfiS.T. Dupont D-Initial
Schmidt
Schmidt Capless RollerballSchmidt Intrinsic
Sensa
Sensa PinstripeSensa MetalsSensa Safari Serengeti CollectionSensa ClassicSensa Mayflower 400th Anniversary Limited Edition
Sheaffer
Sheaffer LegacySheaffer Prelude LacquerSheaffer IonSheaffer IntensitySheaffer ReminderSheaffer VFMSheaffer Dotted Journal
Sherpa
Sherpa Pen CoverSherpa Limited EditionsInserts for SherpaSherpa ‘BIC stick’ Stylus Pen Cover
Stipula Passaporto
U - Z
Visconti
Visconti Homo Sapiens Crystal DreamVisconti Limited Edition Blue LagoonVisconti Homo Sapiens Lava ColorVisconti Homo Sapiens SkylightVisconti Opera Master PolynesiaVisconti Homo Sapiens MagmaVisconti BreezeVisconti Homo SapiensVisconti RembrandtVisconti van GoghVisconti BallpointsVisconti Fountain PensVisconti Rollerballs
Waldmann
CommanderEco
Waterman
Waterman Carene LacquerWaterman Expert LacquerWaterman EmblèmeWaterman Hemisphere French RivieraWaterman Hemisphere CloseoutWaterman Ballpoint PensWaterman Fountain PensWaterman Rollerball Pens
Yookers
Yookers ErosYookers MetisYookers Yooth
YSTUDIO
Refill Central
Refills for Brands A - L
Colorado Pen Branded Inks5280 Refills
Ballpoint Refills for 5280Fountain Pen Refills for 5280Rollerball Refills for 5280
Refills for Aurora
Ballpoint Refills for AuroraFountain Pen Refills for AuroraRollerball Refills for Aurora
Refills for American Pen CompanyRefills for Cartier
Ballpoint Refills for CartierFountain Pen Refills for CartierRollerball Refills for Cartier
ColorverseRefills for Conklin
Ballpoint Refills for ConklinFountain Pen Refills for ConklinRollerball Refills for Conklin
Refills for Cross
Ballpoint Refills for CrossFountain Pen Refills for CrossMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for CrossRollerball Refills for Cross
Refills for Fisher
Ballpoint Refills for FisherMulti-Pen Refills for Fisher
Refills for Lamy
Ballpoint Refills for LamyFountain Pen Refills for LamyMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for Lamy
Refills for Brands M - P
Refills for The Metropolitan Museum of Art
Ballpoint Refills Metropolitan Museum ArtFountain Pen Refills Metropolitan Museum of ArtRollerball Refills for Metropolitan Museum of Art
Refills for Montblanc
Ballpoint Refills for MontblancFountain Pen Refills for MontblancRollerball Refills for MontblancMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for Montblanc
Refills For Montegrappa
Ballpoint Refills for MontegrappaFountain Pen Refills for MontegrappaRollerball Refills for Montegrappa
Refills for Monteverde
Ballpoint Refills for MonteverdeFountain Pen Refills for MonteverdeMulti-Pen and Pencil Monteverde RefillsRollerball Refills for Monteverde
Refills for Parker
5th Refills for ParkerBallpoint Refills for ParkerFountain Pen Refills for ParkerRollerball Refills for Parker
Refills for Pelikan
Ballpoint Refills for PelikanFountain Pen Refills for PelikanRollerball Refills for Pelikan
Refills for PineiderRefills for Porsche Design
Ballpoint Refills for Porsche DesignFountain Pen Refills for Porsche DesignPencil Refills for Porsche DesignRollerball Refills for Porsche Design
Refills for Brands Q - T
Refills for Regal
Ballpoint Refills for RegalFountain Pen Refills for RegalRollerball Refills for Regal
Refills for Retro 1951
Fountain Pen Refills for Retro 1951Multi-Pen and Pencil Retro 1951 RefillsBallpoint & Rollerball Refills for Retro 1951Traveler Refills for Retro 1951
Refills for Rotring
Ballpoint Refills for RotringFountain Pen Refills for RotringMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for RotringRollerball Refills for Rotring
Refills for S.T. Dupont
Ballpoint Refills for ST DupontFountain Pen Refills for ST DupontMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for ST DupontRollerball Refills for ST Dupont
Refills for Schmidt
Schmidt Ballpoint RefillsSchmidt Rollerball Refills
Refills for Sensa
Ballpoint Refills for SensaFountain Pen Refills for SensaRollerball Refills for Sensa
Refills for Sheaffer
Ballpoint Refills for SheafferFountain Pen Refills for SheafferRollerball Refills for Sheaffer
Refills for Tombow
Fountain Pen Refills for TombowRollerball Refills for Tombow
Refills for Brands U - Z
Refills for Visconti
Ballpoint Refills for ViscontiEco Roller Refills for ViscontiFountain Pen Refills for ViscontiRollerball Refills for Visconti
Refills for Waterford
Ballpoint Refills for WaterfordFountain Pen Refills for WaterfordMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for WaterfordRollerball Refills for Waterford
Refills for Waterman
Ballpoint Refills for WatermanFountain Pen Refills for WatermanMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for WatermanRollerball Refills for Waterman
Refills for Yookers
Refill type
Ballpoint RefillsMulti-Pen RefillsFountain Pen Ink and RefillsFountain Pen Bottled Ink ConvertersRollerball / Fineliner RefillsPencil Lead and Eraser RefillsParker Style Ballpoint RefillsStandard International Ink CartridgesUniversal Standard Rollerball Refills
Shop By Pen Type
BallpointsFountain PensLiquid Ink WritersRollerball PensPencilsCalligraphy
Accessories
Pen CasesNotepadsPen ChestsPen HolderLeather Folios
OutletFAQs
Who We AreEngravingOrder FAQsPen FAQs
Fountain Pen FAQsRollerball FAQsBallpoint FAQsMulti / Pencil FAQs
Gift CertificateShipping RatesReturn PolicyRepair / WarrantyContact Your BrandContact Us
Subscribe
E-Gift CertificateWork-a-DayBeginning WritersShop Our Brands
A - L
5280
5280 Ambassador Collection5280 Aspen Collection5280 Aspire Collection5280 Ebonite5280 Majestic Collection5280 Opera
American Pen Company
Bronze MinimalistBallpoint WritingLiquid Ink Ball WritingLimited Edition Valentine's SetFountain Pen WritingIndependence Signature TipLeather FoliosLeather CasesSketch Pencil and Highlighting
Aurora
Aurora Ipsilon DemoAurora Duo Cart Fountain PenAurora Fountain PensAurora Rollerballs
BENU
BrioletteMinimaTattoo
Conklin
Conklin All American Turquoise SerenityConklin All American Golden WalnutConklin Limited Edition Endura Abalone RosegoldConklin DuraFlex DemonstratorConklin All American Courage Ltd. Ed.Conklin Limited Edition All American EbonyConklin Heritage Word GaugeConklin Duraflex Limited Edition ElementsConklin All American
Cross
Cross 2020 Year of the RatCross Townsend for Scuderia FerrariCross ApogeeCross WanderlustCross Bailey LightCross ATXCross Century IICross TownsendCross Tech3+ Multi-PenCross X SeriesCross BallpointsCross Fountain PensCross Rollerballs
Esterbrook
Esterbrook Estie Maraschino CherryEsterbrook Phaeton SetEsterbrook JRCamden CompositionEsterbrook EstieEsterbrook SparkleEsterbrook Nook
Fisher
Fisher Red & Blue Line Cap-O-MaticFisher BrassSpecial Edition Bullet 50th Anniversary Apollo 11Fisher S.E. Cap-O-Matic 50th Anniversary Apollo 11Fisher Clutch Space PenFisher Original Astronaut Space PenFisher Bullet Space PenFisher Telescoping Space PenFisher X-750 Stylus
LeBOEUF
LeBOEUF PilgrimLeBOEUF Springfield
M - P
Montegrappa
Montegrappa Tulip for Team FoxMontegrappa Copper MuleMontegrappa BallpointsMontegrappa Fountain PensMontegrappa Rollerballs
Monteverde
Monteverde MegaMonteverde 20th Anniversary Limited Edition InnovaMonteverde Limited Edition Regatta ExplorersMonteverde Monza 3Monteverde Regatta Sport AlluraMonteverde Sweet LifeMonteverde RitmaMonteverde Tool Pen EdgeMonteverde ImpressaMonteverde Aldo DomaniMonteverde Giant SequoiaMonteverde PrimaMonteverde Ballpoint PensMonteverde Fountain PensMonteverde Rollerball Pens
Padrino
Padrino TrendPadrino GridPadrino Fiore Pen SetPadrino Multi-PenPadrino Pixie
Parker
Parker Duofold ClassicParker Sonnet SterlingParker Sonnet CoreParker Jotter XLParker JotterParker BallpointsParker Fountain PensParker Rollerballs
Pineider
Pineider Back To The Future Limited EditionPineider HoneycombPineider Avatar URPineider Avatar UR DemonstratorPineider Hollywood Journal
Q - T
Regal
Regal British MuseumRegal CrownRegal ElizabethRegal Henry
S.T. Dupont
S.T. Dupont DéfiS.T. Dupont D-Initial
Schmidt
Schmidt Capless RollerballSchmidt Intrinsic
Sensa
Sensa PinstripeSensa MetalsSensa Safari Serengeti CollectionSensa ClassicSensa Mayflower 400th Anniversary Limited Edition
Sheaffer
Sheaffer LegacySheaffer Prelude LacquerSheaffer IonSheaffer IntensitySheaffer ReminderSheaffer VFMSheaffer Dotted Journal
Sherpa
Sherpa Pen CoverSherpa Limited EditionsInserts for SherpaSherpa ‘BIC stick’ Stylus Pen Cover
Stipula Passaporto
U - Z
Visconti
Visconti Homo Sapiens Crystal DreamVisconti Limited Edition Blue LagoonVisconti Homo Sapiens Lava ColorVisconti Homo Sapiens SkylightVisconti Opera Master PolynesiaVisconti Homo Sapiens MagmaVisconti BreezeVisconti Homo SapiensVisconti RembrandtVisconti van GoghVisconti BallpointsVisconti Fountain PensVisconti Rollerballs
Waldmann
CommanderEco
Waterman
Waterman Carene LacquerWaterman Expert LacquerWaterman EmblèmeWaterman Hemisphere French RivieraWaterman Hemisphere CloseoutWaterman Ballpoint PensWaterman Fountain PensWaterman Rollerball Pens
Yookers
Yookers ErosYookers MetisYookers Yooth
YSTUDIO
Refill Central
Refills for Brands A - L
Colorado Pen Branded Inks5280 Refills
Ballpoint Refills for 5280Fountain Pen Refills for 5280Rollerball Refills for 5280
Refills for Aurora
Ballpoint Refills for AuroraFountain Pen Refills for AuroraRollerball Refills for Aurora
Refills for American Pen CompanyRefills for Cartier
Ballpoint Refills for CartierFountain Pen Refills for CartierRollerball Refills for Cartier
ColorverseRefills for Conklin
Ballpoint Refills for ConklinFountain Pen Refills for ConklinRollerball Refills for Conklin
Refills for Cross
Ballpoint Refills for CrossFountain Pen Refills for CrossMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for CrossRollerball Refills for Cross
Refills for Fisher
Ballpoint Refills for FisherMulti-Pen Refills for Fisher
Refills for Lamy
Ballpoint Refills for LamyFountain Pen Refills for LamyMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for Lamy
Refills for Brands M - P
Refills for The Metropolitan Museum of Art
Ballpoint Refills Metropolitan Museum ArtFountain Pen Refills Metropolitan Museum of ArtRollerball Refills for Metropolitan Museum of Art
Refills for Montblanc
Ballpoint Refills for MontblancFountain Pen Refills for MontblancRollerball Refills for MontblancMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for Montblanc
Refills For Montegrappa
Ballpoint Refills for MontegrappaFountain Pen Refills for MontegrappaRollerball Refills for Montegrappa
Refills for Monteverde
Ballpoint Refills for MonteverdeFountain Pen Refills for MonteverdeMulti-Pen and Pencil Monteverde RefillsRollerball Refills for Monteverde
Refills for Parker
5th Refills for ParkerBallpoint Refills for ParkerFountain Pen Refills for ParkerRollerball Refills for Parker
Refills for Pelikan
Ballpoint Refills for PelikanFountain Pen Refills for PelikanRollerball Refills for Pelikan
Refills for PineiderRefills for Porsche Design
Ballpoint Refills for Porsche DesignFountain Pen Refills for Porsche DesignPencil Refills for Porsche DesignRollerball Refills for Porsche Design
Refills for Brands Q - T
Refills for Regal
Ballpoint Refills for RegalFountain Pen Refills for RegalRollerball Refills for Regal
Refills for Retro 1951
Fountain Pen Refills for Retro 1951Multi-Pen and Pencil Retro 1951 RefillsBallpoint & Rollerball Refills for Retro 1951Traveler Refills for Retro 1951
Refills for Rotring
Ballpoint Refills for RotringFountain Pen Refills for RotringMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for RotringRollerball Refills for Rotring
Refills for S.T. Dupont
Ballpoint Refills for ST DupontFountain Pen Refills for ST DupontMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for ST DupontRollerball Refills for ST Dupont
Refills for Schmidt
Schmidt Ballpoint RefillsSchmidt Rollerball Refills
Refills for Sensa
Ballpoint Refills for SensaFountain Pen Refills for SensaRollerball Refills for Sensa
Refills for Sheaffer
Ballpoint Refills for SheafferFountain Pen Refills for SheafferRollerball Refills for Sheaffer
Refills for Tombow
Fountain Pen Refills for TombowRollerball Refills for Tombow
Refills for Brands U - Z
Refills for Visconti
Ballpoint Refills for ViscontiEco Roller Refills for ViscontiFountain Pen Refills for ViscontiRollerball Refills for Visconti
Refills for Waterford
Ballpoint Refills for WaterfordFountain Pen Refills for WaterfordMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for WaterfordRollerball Refills for Waterford
Refills for Waterman
Ballpoint Refills for WatermanFountain Pen Refills for WatermanMulti-Pen and Pencil Refills for WatermanRollerball Refills for Waterman
Refills for Yookers
Refill type
Ballpoint RefillsMulti-Pen RefillsFountain Pen Ink and RefillsFountain Pen Bottled Ink ConvertersRollerball / Fineliner RefillsPencil Lead and Eraser RefillsParker Style Ballpoint RefillsStandard International Ink CartridgesUniversal Standard Rollerball Refills
Shop By Pen Type
BallpointsFountain PensLiquid Ink WritersRollerball PensPencilsCalligraphy
Accessories
Pen CasesNotepadsPen ChestsPen HolderLeather Folios
OutletFAQs
Who We AreEngravingOrder FAQsPen FAQs
Fountain Pen FAQsRollerball FAQsBallpoint FAQsMulti / Pencil FAQs
Gift CertificateShipping RatesReturn PolicyRepair / WarrantyContact Your BrandContact Us
Privacy Policy
Effective date: October 24, 2018
Colorado Pen ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.coloradopen.com website.
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use coloradopen.com and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve coloradopen.com. By using coloradopen.com, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.coloradopen.com
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using coloradopen.com, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how coloradopen.com is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on coloradopen.com and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate coloradopen.com.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Colorado Pen uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain coloradopen.com
To notify you about changes to coloradopen.com
To allow you to participate in interactive features of coloradopen.com when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve coloradopen.com
To monitor the usage of coloradopen.com
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Colorado Pen will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
Colorado Pen may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of Colorado Pen
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of coloradopen.com or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate coloradopen.com ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform coloradopen.com-related services or to assist us in analyzing how coloradopen.com is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of coloradopen.com.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of coloradopen.com. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
You can opt-out of having made your activity on coloradopen.com available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links To Other Sites
Coloradopen.com may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: cpdirect@coloradopen.com
By visiting this page on our website: https://www.coloradopen.com/privacy
By phone number: 720-259-1601
ACCOUNT LINKSBECOME A COLORADO PEN MEMBERRETURN POLICYPRIVACY POLICY
CONTACT USCALL: 720.259.1601EMAIL: cpdirect@coloradopen.com608 Garrison Street Suite FLakewood, CO 80215
×
Price:
Actual Price:
Add to Cart
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price." As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
Our price is lower than the manufacturer's "minimum advertised price." As a result, we cannot show you the price in catalog or the product page.
